[
	{
		"question": "random",
		"answer": "sequential",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "familiar",
		"answer": "unknown",
		"otherAnswers": ["novel", "strange"]
	},
	{
		"question": "quirky",
		"answer": "conventional",
		"otherAnswers": ["traditional"]
	},
	{
		"question": "swim",
		"answer": "sink",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "peace",
		"answer": "war",
		"otherAnswers": ["disharmony"]
	},
	{
		"question": "latter",
		"answer": "former",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "famous",
		"answer": "anonymous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "diligent",
		"answer": "slapdash",
		"otherAnswers": ["careless", "negligent", "sloppy"]
	},
	{
		"question": "conclude",
		"answer": "initiate",
		"otherAnswers": ["commence"]
	},
	{
		"question": "ultimate",
		"answer": "initial",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "distraught",
		"answer": "tranquil",
		"otherAnswers": ["calm"]
	},
	{
		"question": "clarify",
		"answer": "confuse",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "uncomfortable",
		"answer": "cosy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "light",
		"answer": "dark",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "positive",
		"answer": "negative",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "straight",
		"answer": "crooked",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "resolute",
		"answer": "yielding",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "cleanse",
		"answer": "pollute",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "insecure",
		"answer": "assured",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "soak",
		"answer": "absorb",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "nervous",
		"answer": "fearless",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "major",
		"answer": "minor",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "inaccurate",
		"answer": "precise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "pacify",
		"answer": "provoke",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "coarse",
		"answer": "smooth",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fragile",
		"answer": "resilient",
		"otherAnswers": ["robust"]
	},
	{
		"question": "relapse",
		"answer": "recover",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "overdue",
		"answer": "prompt",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "feminine",
		"answer": "masculine",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "radiant",
		"answer": "dull",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "consonant",
		"answer": "vowel",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "straight",
		"answer": "wavy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "inflexible",
		"answer": "bendy",
		"otherAnswers": ["yielding"]
	},
	{
		"question": "hope",
		"answer": "despair",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "gentle",
		"answer": "ferocious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "obscure",
		"answer": "prominent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "bellow",
		"answer": "whisper",
		"otherAnswers": ["murmur"]
	},
	{
		"question": "spring",
		"answer": "autumn",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "progress",
		"answer": "decline",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hated",
		"answer": "loved",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "criticism",
		"answer": "praise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fit",
		"answer": "unhealthy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "incapable",
		"answer": "competent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "vulgar",
		"answer": "polite",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "conspicuous",
		"answer": "concealed",
		"otherAnswers": ["obscured"]
	},
	{
		"question": "short",
		"answer": "tall",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "quits",
		"answer": "endures",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "enlarged",
		"answer": "diminished",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "minimum",
		"answer": "maximum",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "shabby",
		"answer": "opulent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "selfish",
		"answer": "magnanimous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ominous",
		"answer": "auspicious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "praise",
		"answer": "scorn",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "soft",
		"answer": "hard",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "abandon",
		"answer": "keep",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sauntered",
		"answer": "raced",
		"otherAnswers": ["sprinted"]
	},
	{
		"question": "unequal",
		"answer": "fair",
		"otherAnswers": ["balanced"]
	},
	{
		"question": "reckless",
		"answer": "cautious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "straight",
		"answer": "curved",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "encourages",
		"answer": "undermines",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hasty",
		"answer": "leisurely",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "crucial",
		"answer": "unnecessary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unaware",
		"answer": "alert",
		"otherAnswers": ["astute"]
	},
	{
		"question": "lower",
		"answer": "evelate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "present",
		"answer": "absent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "bland",
		"answer": "spicy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "virtuous",
		"answer": "wicked",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "winter",
		"answer": "summer",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "benign",
		"answer": "malevolent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "appreciate",
		"answer": "loathe",
		"otherAnswers": ["dislike", "despise"]
	},
	{
		"question": "alike",
		"answer": "dissimilar",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "intentional",
		"answer": "unplanned",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "exceptional",
		"answer": "ordinary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "vivid",
		"answer": "colourless",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "transparent",
		"answer": "opaque",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "optimistic",
		"answer": "gloomy",
		"otherAnswers": ["pessimistic"]
	},
	{
		"question": "rigid",
		"answer": "flexible",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "tragic",
		"answer": "comical",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "base",
		"answer": "apex",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "whole",
		"answer": "fraction",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "improbable",
		"answer": "certain",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "steep",
		"answer": "flat",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "flabby",
		"answer": "firm",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hideous",
		"answer": "beautiful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "passive",
		"answer": "active",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "infuriate",
		"answer": "appease",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "frugal",
		"answer": "luxurious",
		"otherAnswers": ["extravagant"]
	},
	{
		"question": "profit",
		"answer": "loss",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "common",
		"answer": "rare",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "elated",
		"answer": "dejected",
		"otherAnswers": ["downhearted", "morose"]
	},
	{
		"question": "justify",
		"answer": "condemn",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "central",
		"answer": "peripheral",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "discourage",
		"answer": "cajole",
		"otherAnswers": ["coax"]
	},
	{
		"question": "complicated",
		"answer": "simple",
		"otherAnswers": ["straightforward"]
	},
	{
		"question": "plausible",
		"answer": "unlikely",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dives",
		"answer": "ascends",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "abolish",
		"answer": "establish",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "absorb",
		"answer": "drench",
		"otherAnswers": ["ooze"]
	},
	{
		"question": "public",
		"answer": "private",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "worst",
		"answer": "best",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "righteous",
		"answer": "wicked",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "severe",
		"answer": "mild",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unhelpful",
		"answer": "obliging",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "partial",
		"answer": "complete",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "compulsory",
		"answer": "voluntary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "wary",
		"answer": "reckless",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "purchase",
		"answer": "sell",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "eager",
		"answer": "indifferent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "skinny",
		"answer": "plumb",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "solitary",
		"answer": "gregarious",
		"otherAnswers": ["accompanied"]
	},
	{
		"question": "loss",
		"answer": "profit",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "rebellious",
		"answer": "compliant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "callous",
		"answer": "compassionate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "plummets",
		"answer": "soars",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "used",
		"answer": "new",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "evade",
		"answer": "seek",
		"otherAnswers": ["target"]
	},
	{
		"question": "certain",
		"answer": "doubtful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "moving",
		"answer": "stationary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ignorant",
		"answer": "knowledgeable",
		"otherAnswers": ["expert"]
	},
	{
		"question": "preceed",
		"answer": "follow",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "liquify",
		"answer": "soldify",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "novice",
		"answer": "expert",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "current",
		"answer": "antiquated",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "clarify",
		"answer": "baffle",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "break",
		"answer": "fix",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "outgoing",
		"answer": "reserved",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dark",
		"answer": "luminous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "enormous",
		"answer": "minute",
		"otherAnswers": ["miniscule"]
	},
	{
		"question": "extravagant",
		"answer": "meagre",
		"otherAnswers": ["frugal", "sparing", "stingy"]
	},
	{
		"question": "renovated",
		"answer": "ruined",
		"otherAnswers": ["delapidated", "worn"]
	},
	{
		"question": "faulty",
		"answer": "functional",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dusk",
		"answer": "dawn",
		"otherAnswers": ["daybreak"]
	},
	{
		"question": "dissuade",
		"answer": "cajole",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "whisper",
		"answer": "shout",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "magnify",
		"answer": "diminish",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "absurd",
		"answer": "serious",
		"otherAnswers": ["logical"]
	},
	{
		"question": "essential",
		"answer": "trivial",
		"otherAnswers": ["irrelevant", "unimportant"]
	},
	{
		"question": "plant",
		"answer": "harvest",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "novice",
		"answer": "expert",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "intolerable",
		"answer": "acceptable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "huge",
		"answer": "diminutive",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "successful",
		"answer": "disastrous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "audacious",
		"answer": "discouraging",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "stale",
		"answer": "fresh",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "attractive",
		"answer": "grotesque",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "taciturn",
		"answer": "talkative",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "reluctant",
		"answer": "keen",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "remarkable",
		"answer": "inconsequential",
		"otherAnswers": ["inconspicuous"]
	},
	{
		"question": "loose",
		"answer": "tight",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "intermittent",
		"answer": "constant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "retreat",
		"answer": "proceed",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "leave",
		"answer": "join",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "repel",
		"answer": "entice",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "solution",
		"answer": "problem",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "indecision",
		"answer": "resolve",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "illegal",
		"answer": "lawful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "stubborn",
		"answer": "reasonable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "certain",
		"answer": "apprehensive",
		"otherAnswers": ["unsure", "vague"]
	},
	{
		"question": "valuable",
		"answer": "worthless",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "awkward",
		"answer": "graceful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fortunate",
		"answer": "unlucky",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "inappropriate",
		"answer": "acceptable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "provoke",
		"answer": "soothe",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "barren",
		"answer": "fertile",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "scatter",
		"answer": "gather",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "apex",
		"answer": "base",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "poverty",
		"answer": "wealth",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "help",
		"answer": "impede",
		"otherAnswers": ["hinder"]
	},
	{
		"question": "sparse",
		"answer": "lush",
		"otherAnswers": ["numerous"]
	},
	{
		"question": "fade",
		"answer": "brighten",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "worthless",
		"answer": "valuable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "abundant",
		"answer": "barren",
		"otherAnswers": ["scarce", "sparce", "scanty"]
	},
	{
		"question": "release",
		"answer": "confine",
		"otherAnswers": ["capture"]
	},
	{
		"question": "extravagant",
		"answer": "sparing",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "reveal",
		"answer": "conceal",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "separate",
		"answer": "united",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "borrow",
		"answer": "grant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "constrained",
		"answer": "unlimited",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "incoherent",
		"answer": "audible",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "forget",
		"answer": "remember",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "victim",
		"answer": "culprit",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "delicate",
		"answer": "robust",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hasten",
		"answer": "dawdle",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "flustered",
		"answer": "calm",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unknown",
		"answer": "infamous",
		"otherAnswers": ["notorious"]
	},
	{
		"question": "succeed",
		"answer": "fail",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "mediocre",
		"answer": "superb",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "wounded",
		"answer": "unscathed",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "vigilant",
		"answer": "inattentive",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "docile",
		"answer": "savage",
		"otherAnswers": ["wild"]
	},
	{
		"question": "thaw",
		"answer": "freeze",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "bottom",
		"answer": "top",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "replenish",
		"answer": "deplete",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "uncivilised",
		"answer": "cultured",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "wash",
		"answer": "soil",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "energetic",
		"answer": "lethargic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "juvenile",
		"answer": "mature",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "volatile",
		"answer": "stable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "faithful",
		"answer": "disloyal",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sweet",
		"answer": "sour",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "pleasant",
		"answer": "nasty",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "venom",
		"answer": "antidote",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fact",
		"answer": "fiction",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ignorance",
		"answer": "knowledge",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dull",
		"answer": "eventful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "retreat",
		"answer": "advance",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "active",
		"answer": "dormant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "lasting",
		"answer": "temporary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "admit",
		"answer": "expel",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "agree",
		"answer": "protest",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "released",
		"answer": "apprehended",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "profound",
		"answer": "superficial",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "untrustworthy",
		"answer": "reputable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "disgrace",
		"answer": "honour",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "solution",
		"answer": "dilemma",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "contradict",
		"answer": "confirm",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "shallow",
		"answer": "deep",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "alike",
		"answer": "different",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "intermittent",
		"answer": "continuous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sharp",
		"answer": "blunt",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "honest",
		"answer": "devious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unnecessary",
		"answer": "crucial",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "complex",
		"answer": "simple",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "scrupulous",
		"answer": "careless",
		"otherAnswers": ["reckless"]
	},
	{
		"question": "forgiving",
		"answer": "vindictive",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "tolerant",
		"answer": "impatient",
		"otherAnswers": ["judgemental"]
	},
	{
		"question": "alive",
		"answer": "deceased",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "perpendicular",
		"answer": "parallel",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "continue",
		"answer": "pause",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "roar",
		"answer": "whisper",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sturdy",
		"answer": "flimsy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "drag",
		"answer": "push",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "subtract",
		"answer": "add",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "stoop",
		"answer": "straighten",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "disperse",
		"answer": "gather",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "different",
		"answer": "similar",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "winter",
		"answer": "summer",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "rejoice",
		"answer": "lament",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "foreboding",
		"answer": "auspicious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "release",
		"answer": "seize",
		"otherAnswers": ["imprison", "capture"]
	},
	{
		"question": "obnoxious",
		"answer": "aromatic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "incompetent",
		"answer": "gifted",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "adjacent",
		"answer": "distant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "combative",
		"answer": "peaceful",
		"otherAnswers": ["compromising"]
	},
	{
		"question": "wilt",
		"answer": "bloom",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "against",
		"answer": "for",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "desire",
		"answer": "despise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "misunderstand",
		"answer": "grasp",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "confuse",
		"answer": "clarify",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unimportant",
		"answer": "noteworthy",
		"otherAnswers": ["essential"]
	},
	{
		"question": "arrogant",
		"answer": "humble",
		"otherAnswers": ["modest"]
	},
	{
		"question": "subdued",
		"answer": "boisterous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "abbreviate",
		"answer": "lengthen",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "harmony",
		"answer": "discord",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "accidental",
		"answer": "deliberate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "industrious",
		"answer": "idle",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "bare",
		"answer": "covered",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "adjacent",
		"answer": "distant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unfair",
		"answer": "just",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "peaceful",
		"answer": "bustling",
		"otherAnswers": ["belligerant", "stormy"]
	},
	{
		"question": "impartiality",
		"answer": "favouritism",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "prosperous",
		"answer": "destitute",
		"otherAnswers": ["poor"]
	},
	{
		"question": "unequalled",
		"answer": "matched",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "speedy",
		"answer": "slow",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "obedient",
		"answer": "insubordinate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "coarse",
		"answer": "smooth",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "permit",
		"answer": "veto",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "customer",
		"answer": "supplier",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "teacher",
		"answer": "student",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unhelpful",
		"answer": "cooperative",
		"otherAnswers": ["supportive", "useful"]
	},
	{
		"question": "confess",
		"answer": "deny",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "catch",
		"answer": "release",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "attack",
		"answer": "defend",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unhealthy",
		"answer": "wholesome",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "expose",
		"answer": "hide",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ceiling",
		"answer": "floor",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "honest",
		"answer": "corrupt",
		"otherAnswers": ["untruthful"]
	},
	{
		"question": "division",
		"answer": "unity",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "placate",
		"answer": "irritate",
		"otherAnswers": ["enrage", "annoy"]
	},
	{
		"question": "insufficient",
		"answer": "enough",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "turbulent",
		"answer": "calm",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "withdrawn",
		"answer": "outgoing",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "rigid",
		"answer": "pliable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fresh",
		"answer": "stale",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "transparent",
		"answer": "opaque",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "departure",
		"answer": "arrival",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "compliment",
		"answer": "rebuke",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "disagreement",
		"answer": "accord",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "vivid",
		"answer": "dull",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sprint",
		"answer": "saunter",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "victor",
		"answer": "loser",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "myth",
		"answer": "fact",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "gain",
		"answer": "forfeit",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "follow",
		"answer": "lead",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "despised",
		"answer": "popular",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unclear",
		"answer": "distinct",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "wild",
		"answer": "tame",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "generous",
		"answer": "stingy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "release",
		"answer": "imprison",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "devious",
		"answer": "honest",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "combine",
		"answer": "separate",
		"otherAnswers": ["isolate"]
	},
	{
		"question": "dismiss",
		"answer": "appreciate",
		"otherAnswers": ["value"]
	},
	{
		"question": "generous",
		"answer": "greedy",
		"otherAnswers": ["miserly", "selfish"]
	},
	{
		"question": "organised",
		"answer": "chaotic",
		"otherAnswers": ["anarchic"]
	},
	{
		"question": "costly",
		"answer": "free",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "tomorrow",
		"answer": "yesterday",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "blame",
		"answer": "praise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "miserly",
		"answer": "generous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "cruel",
		"answer": "compassionate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "confess",
		"answer": "deny",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "promote",
		"answer": "hamper",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "casual",
		"answer": "formal",
		"otherAnswers": ["solemn"]
	},
	{
		"question": "vindictive",
		"answer": "forgiving",
		"otherAnswers": ["merciful"]
	},
	{
		"question": "unique",
		"answer": "routine",
		"otherAnswers": ["regular"]
	},
	{
		"question": "delayed",
		"answer": "premature",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sinking",
		"answer": "floating",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "repair",
		"answer": "break",
		"otherAnswers": ["rupture"]
	},
	{
		"question": "freeze",
		"answer": "melt",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "courage",
		"answer": "cowardice",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unlikely",
		"answer": "inevitable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "clever",
		"answer": "stupid",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "relieved",
		"answer": "worried",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "miserly",
		"answer": "generous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "expose",
		"answer": "conceal",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "leave",
		"answer": "remain",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "singular",
		"answer": "plural",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "approximately",
		"answer": "exactly",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "private",
		"answer": "communal",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "prey",
		"answer": "predator",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "stretch",
		"answer": "contract",
		"otherAnswers": ["shrink", "shrivel"]
	},
	{
		"question": "release",
		"answer": "capture",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "inept",
		"answer": "capable",
		"otherAnswers": ["able", "expert"]
	},
	{
		"question": "kind",
		"answer": "callous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "clarify",
		"answer": "confuse",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "disagree",
		"answer": "concur",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "lazy",
		"answer": "diligent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "occupied",
		"answer": "vacant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "harmony",
		"answer": "discord",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "amiable",
		"answer": "hostile",
		"otherAnswers": ["unfriendly", "combative"]
	},
	{
		"question": "admire",
		"answer": "detest",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "combine",
		"answer": "seperate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "below",
		"answer": "above",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "genuine",
		"answer": "fake",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "west",
		"answer": "east",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unrefined",
		"answer": "cultured",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "serene",
		"answer": "agitated",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "incompetent",
		"answer": "skilled",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "erratic",
		"answer": "ordered",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "exquisite",
		"answer": "repugnant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "shorten",
		"answer": "prolong",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "putrid",
		"answer": "fresh",
		"otherAnswers": ["wholesome"]
	},
	{
		"question": "cautious",
		"answer": "rash",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "stunning",
		"answer": "revolting",
		"otherAnswers": ["grotesque", "ugly"]
	},
	{
		"question": "strict",
		"answer": "lenient",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "raw",
		"answer": "cooked",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "moist",
		"answer": "arid",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "immaculate",
		"answer": "filthy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "intricate",
		"answer": "simple",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "scatter",
		"answer": "gather",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "condemn",
		"answer": "praise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "compassionate",
		"answer": "uncaring",
		"otherAnswers": ["callous"]
	},
	{
		"question": "doubt",
		"answer": "trust",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "static",
		"answer": "mobile",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fierce",
		"answer": "tame",
		"otherAnswers": ["placid", "calm"]
	},
	{
		"question": "agile",
		"answer": "inflexible",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "knot",
		"answer": "untie",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "mountain",
		"answer": "valley",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dispicable",
		"answer": "commendable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "withdraw",
		"answer": "deposit",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "rest",
		"answer": "labour",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "join",
		"answer": "disconnect",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "awkward",
		"answer": "graceful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "intolerant",
		"answer": "patient",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "constant",
		"answer": "variable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "far",
		"answer": "close",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "single",
		"answer": "double",
		"otherAnswers": ["multiple", "numerous"]
	},
	{
		"question": "frenzied",
		"answer": "serene",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "respectful",
		"answer": "flippant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "icy",
		"answer": "boiling",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "reveal",
		"answer": "disguise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "exit",
		"answer": "entrance",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "futile",
		"answer": "effective",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "wane",
		"answer": "wax",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "crowded",
		"answer": "deserted",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "cry",
		"answer": "laugh",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "free",
		"answer": "restricted",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "deny",
		"answer": "confirm",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "close",
		"answer": "distant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ignite",
		"answer": "extinguish",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "captivity",
		"answer": "liberty",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "slack",
		"answer": "taut",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "imaginary",
		"answer": "real",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "scowl",
		"answer": "grin",
		"otherAnswers": ["smile"]
	},
	{
		"question": "fake",
		"answer": "genuine",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "simple",
		"answer": "intricate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "copy",
		"answer": "original",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "logical",
		"answer": "irrational",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "heartbroken",
		"answer": "overjoyed",
		"otherAnswers": ["elated"]
	},
	{
		"question": "crooked",
		"answer": "straight",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hatred",
		"answer": "affection",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "clarification",
		"answer": "confusion",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "general",
		"answer": "specific",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "delicious",
		"answer": "inedible",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "apprehensive",
		"answer": "composed",
		"otherAnswers": ["collected"]
	},
	{
		"question": "monotonous",
		"answer": "exciting",
		"otherAnswers": ["varied", "interesting"]
	},
	{
		"question": "confirmation",
		"answer": "denial",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "back",
		"answer": "front",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "erratic",
		"answer": "stable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "understanding",
		"answer": "intolerant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ambiguous",
		"answer": "precise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "doubt",
		"answer": "believe",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "denies",
		"answer": "acknowledges",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "weird",
		"answer": "ordinary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "concur",
		"answer": "disagree",
		"otherAnswers": ["argue"]
	},
	{
		"question": "reduce",
		"answer": "exacerbate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "expensive",
		"answer": "cheap",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "opaque",
		"answer": "transparent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "early",
		"answer": "late",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "comfort",
		"answer": "harass",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "wither",
		"answer": "blossom",
		"otherAnswers": ["flourish"]
	},
	{
		"question": "foolish",
		"answer": "wise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "straighten",
		"answer": "bend",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "flushed",
		"answer": "pallid",
		"otherAnswers": ["pale"]
	},
	{
		"question": "urban",
		"answer": "rural",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "parch",
		"answer": "hydrate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "seldom",
		"answer": "frequent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hidden",
		"answer": "conspicuous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "tense",
		"answer": "relaxed",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "flamboyant",
		"answer": "dull",
		"otherAnswers": ["shy"]
	},
	{
		"question": "defend",
		"answer": "denounce",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "perish",
		"answer": "revive",
		"otherAnswers": ["live"]
	},
	{
		"question": "common",
		"answer": "unusual",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "satisfied",
		"answer": "disappointed",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "impartial",
		"answer": "prejudiced",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "invincible",
		"answer": "vanquished",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "pessimist",
		"answer": "optimist",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "all",
		"answer": "none",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "overhead",
		"answer": "subterranean",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sucking",
		"answer": "blowing",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "identical",
		"answer": "different",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "avoid",
		"answer": "confront",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "valiant",
		"answer": "timid",
		"otherAnswers": ["nervous", "cowardly"]
	},
	{
		"question": "covert",
		"answer": "open",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "obnoxious",
		"answer": "delightful",
		"otherAnswers": ["pleasant", "likeable"]
	},
	{
		"question": "despise",
		"answer": "love",
		"otherAnswers": ["admire"]
	},
	{
		"question": "pristine",
		"answer": "shabby",
		"otherAnswers": ["drab", "soiled"]
	},
	{
		"question": "grotesque",
		"answer": "beautiful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "conceal",
		"answer": "divulge",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "level",
		"answer": "steep",
		"otherAnswers": ["sloping"]
	},
	{
		"question": "tedious",
		"answer": "dramatic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "foolish",
		"answer": "prudent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "decline",
		"answer": "prosper",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sensible",
		"answer": "ludicrous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "lenient",
		"answer": "strict",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "delete",
		"answer": "include",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "lethargic",
		"answer": "vigorous",
		"otherAnswers": ["lively", "active"]
	},
	{
		"question": "finite",
		"answer": "boundless",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "drain",
		"answer": "fill",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "preceding",
		"answer": "following",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "right",
		"answer": "left",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "discouraging",
		"answer": "inspirational",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "miss",
		"answer": "hit",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "arid",
		"answer": "wet",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "connection",
		"answer": "gap",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "deceiving",
		"answer": "honest",
		"otherAnswers": ["truthful", "frank"]
	},
	{
		"question": "singular",
		"answer": "plural",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "slow",
		"answer": "accelerate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "stale",
		"answer": "fresh",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "theoretical",
		"answer": "proven",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "flexible",
		"answer": "adamant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "villain",
		"answer": "hero",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "discord",
		"answer": "harmony",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "friendship",
		"answer": "feud",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dispicable",
		"answer": "agreeable",
		"otherAnswers": ["admirable"]
	},
	{
		"question": "reveal",
		"answer": "camouflage",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "colossal",
		"answer": "tiny",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "constant",
		"answer": "variable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "lazy",
		"answer": "industrious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "rudeness",
		"answer": "courtesy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "future",
		"answer": "past",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ancestor",
		"answer": "descendant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ambiguous",
		"answer": "transparent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "misfortune",
		"answer": "luck",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "never",
		"answer": "always",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "safety",
		"answer": "peril",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "accomplishment",
		"answer": "failure",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "refuse",
		"answer": "accept",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "candid",
		"answer": "mysterious",
		"otherAnswers": ["secretive"]
	},
	{
		"question": "boss",
		"answer": "employee",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "permanent",
		"answer": "temporary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "proficient",
		"answer": "inept",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "maximum",
		"answer": "minimum",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "glance",
		"answer": "stare",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fact",
		"answer": "fable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "bizarre",
		"answer": "ordinary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "segment",
		"answer": "whole",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "flow",
		"answer": "ebb",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "alleviate",
		"answer": "aggravate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "lessen",
		"answer": "amplify",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "exclude",
		"answer": "involve",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "famous",
		"answer": "anonymous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "improbable",
		"answer": "possible",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "destruction",
		"answer": "creation",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "silent",
		"answer": "garrulous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "atrocious",
		"answer": "wonderful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "accidental",
		"answer": "intentional",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "peace",
		"answer": "war",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "harsh",
		"answer": "mild",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "taciturn",
		"answer": "talkative",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "follow",
		"answer": "lead",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "vanish",
		"answer": "appear",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "protect",
		"answer": "harm",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "strange",
		"answer": "familiar",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "always",
		"answer": "never",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "uneven",
		"answer": "level",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "roomy",
		"answer": "cramped",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hasten",
		"answer": "loiter",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "persevere",
		"answer": "discontinue",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "bumpy",
		"answer": "smooth",
		"otherAnswers": ["flat", "level"]
	},
	{
		"question": "compress",
		"answer": "expand",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "reknowned",
		"answer": "unknown",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "polar",
		"answer": "tropical",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "demolish",
		"answer": "construct",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "swell",
		"answer": "contract",
		"otherAnswers": ["compress"]
	},
	{
		"question": "tragedy",
		"answer": "comedy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unruly",
		"answer": "obedient",
		"otherAnswers": ["compliant", "docile"]
	},
	{
		"question": "adult",
		"answer": "infant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "explicit",
		"answer": "vague",
		"otherAnswers": ["unclear", "ambiguous"]
	},
	{
		"question": "master",
		"answer": "servant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "purify",
		"answer": "contaminate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "headstrong",
		"answer": "docile",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "acknowledges",
		"answer": "ignores",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "avid",
		"answer": "indifferent",
		"otherAnswers": ["uninterested"]
	},
	{
		"question": "precarious",
		"answer": "secure",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "permit",
		"answer": "forbid",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "donate",
		"answer": "appropriate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "laugh",
		"answer": "cry",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "death",
		"answer": "birth",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "engrossing",
		"answer": "boring",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "giant",
		"answer": "pygmy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "deny",
		"answer": "acknowledge",
		"otherAnswers": ["confess"]
	},
	{
		"question": "inexact",
		"answer": "accurate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ignite",
		"answer": "extinguish",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "insignificant",
		"answer": "precious",
		"otherAnswers": ["important", "vital"]
	},
	{
		"question": "oppress",
		"answer": "encourage",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "good",
		"answer": "mischievous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "vanish",
		"answer": "appear",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "natural",
		"answer": "synthetic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "succinct",
		"answer": "wordy",
		"otherAnswers": ["verbose"]
	},
	{
		"question": "ambitious",
		"answer": "lazy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "pause",
		"answer": "continue",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "shallow",
		"answer": "deep",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "urge",
		"answer": "discourage",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "harmful",
		"answer": "innocuous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "bleak",
		"answer": "bright",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "aggravate",
		"answer": "relieve",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "biased",
		"answer": "impartial",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "commend",
		"answer": "rebuke",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "healthy",
		"answer": "infirm",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "host",
		"answer": "guest",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "permanent",
		"answer": "temporary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "vertical",
		"answer": "horizontal",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "triumph",
		"answer": "lose",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "morose",
		"answer": "jovial",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hinder",
		"answer": "assist",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "malice",
		"answer": "goodwill",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "shrewd",
		"answer": "foolish",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "flood",
		"answer": "drain",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "perimeter",
		"answer": "centre",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sharp",
		"answer": "blunt",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "compassion",
		"answer": "cruelty",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "elementary",
		"answer": "advanced",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "blunt",
		"answer": "tactful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "mediocre",
		"answer": "marvellous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "applaud",
		"answer": "scold",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "miniscule",
		"answer": "gargantuan",
		"otherAnswers": ["immense", "huge"]
	},
	{
		"question": "orderly",
		"answer": "tangled",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "enraged",
		"answer": "soothed",
		"otherAnswers": ["placated"]
	},
	{
		"question": "healthy",
		"answer": "malignant",
		"otherAnswers": ["ailing"]
	},
	{
		"question": "heroic",
		"answer": "cowardly",
		"otherAnswers": ["scared", "craven", "panicky", "spineless"]
	},
	{
		"question": "wisdom",
		"answer": "folly",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "initial",
		"answer": "ultimate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "generosity",
		"answer": "greed",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "foe",
		"answer": "friend",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "detrimental",
		"answer": "beneficial",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "petrified",
		"answer": "confident",
		"otherAnswers": ["assured", "carefree"]
	},
	{
		"question": "messy",
		"answer": "immaculate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "weave",
		"answer": "untwist",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "weary",
		"answer": "energetic",
		"otherAnswers": ["lively", "vigorous"]
	},
	{
		"question": "prudent",
		"answer": "unwise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "started",
		"answer": "concluded",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "optional",
		"answer": "compulsory",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "disapprove",
		"answer": "authorise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "crazy",
		"answer": "sane",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "welcoming",
		"answer": "inhospitable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "tense",
		"answer": "relax",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "rose",
		"answer": "descended",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "arduous",
		"answer": "easy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "happy",
		"answer": "melancholy",
		"otherAnswers": ["morose"]
	},
	{
		"question": "moderate",
		"answer": "extreme",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "vague",
		"answer": "apparent",
		"otherAnswers": ["precise"]
	}
]
